

About Me

A Graphic Designer with six years of experience working as the lead designer of Studio Shodwe and overseeing the individual project for brand development. Expert in video and layout creation, which is proved to be a valuable addition to developing the company's design project. Always use the out-of-the-box principle in creating the project, so it will come out with more powerful exposure and strength to attract public attention to the promotion campaign. Hard worker and have experience in leading a team of designers, and I can't wait to implement my skill and experience in your company.

Education

Bachelor of Arts in Communication Visual Design Connor Hamilton University

2010 - 2014

GPA: 3.85

Skill

Photo editing Web layout design Social media analysis



Experience

Studio Shodwe | 2016 - 2017

Graphic Designer Intern

- Partnered with other interns to create a new layout for the recipe book by Aaron Loeb. It receives a satisfactory response from the author of the book. He said it represents his cooking purpose and style perfectly.
- Edited still photo for display on Fauget online store mobile app.

(Studio Shodwe | 2017 - Present)

Professional Graphic Designer

- Created a compilation of 55+ still images for the design template that Studio Shodwe has been using on many projects.
- Collaborated with the sales team to create the sales content for the promotion campaign of the Ingoude Company's 10th Anniversary.

